Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, 1967-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1967-1993, I.; Item 1-149
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 39, 12 May 1977, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: CPC #9: New abstraction Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Concert titled The new abstraction, concert no. 9 in the series, 
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_039_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_039_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_039_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_039_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_039_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 40, 12 May 1977, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: CPC #9 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Katherine Cornell Theatre, University at Buffalo Concert titled The new abstraction, concert no. 9 in the series, The contemporary piano. Contents stated here are for entire program but nothing is stated on tape so contents must be verified. Derivative files created: 4 (Box 1, Item 40)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_040_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_040_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_040_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_040_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_040_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_040_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_040_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_040_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_040_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_040_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 41, 15 May 1977, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: CPC #10: Signoff Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello; Thomas Halpin, violin Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Concert titled Signoff, concert no. 10 in the series, The contemporary piano. Derivative files created: 11 (Box 1, Item 41)
    Contents: Copland: Blues no. 1; Smit: Finale/Sonata; Satie: Choses vue à droite et gauche; Feldman: Durations 2; Cowell: Hymn and Fuging; Hiller: Violin sonata no.2 (2nd and 3rd mvt); Bartók: Sonata for solo violin. Chaconne and fugue; Mikhashoff: Prelude, variations, and fugue; Cage: Tossed... -- Music for Marcel Duchamps -- 4'33"
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_041_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_041_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_041_02-05pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_041_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_041_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_041_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_041_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_041_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_041_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_041_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_041_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_041_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_041_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_041_02-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 42, 6 March 1992, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Cage: Concert. Label: Concert for piano and orchestra Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Northwestern University Contemporary Music Ensemble; Don Owens, director Recording location: Northwestern University (Evanston, Ill.). Pick-Staiger Concert Hall Dolby B From concert titled Concertos of John Cage which also included Concerto for prepared piano and chamber orchestra and 108 (for Cello and ensemble) Derivative files created: 1 (Box 1, Item 42)
    Contents: Cage: Concert for piano and orchestra
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_042_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_042_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_042_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 43, 14 March 1976, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Cambiata Soloists Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Cambiata Soloists Recording location: University of St. Thomas (Houston, Texas) Side A is the 2nd half of a concert titled Old wine in new bottles; Side B is from a 9 June 1972 concert at University of Texas at Austin Derivative files created: 5 (Box 1, Item 43)
    Contents: Mikhashoff-Schmidt: The masque of the winter's tale; Mikhashoff: Tiento para el espejo; Stravinsky: Three pieces for clarinet solo; Fricker: Aubade for alto sax and piano; Poulenc: Trio
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_043_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_043_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_043_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_043_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_043_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_043_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_043_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_043_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_043_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_043_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_043_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_043_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 44, 9 June 1972, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Cambiata Soloists 1972 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Mary Jungerman, clarinet; Phyllis Herdliska, viola; Amy Winn, flute; Walker Smith, saxophone; Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano Recording location: University of Texas at Houston Dolby Concert titled: The broken consort: unusual combinations from Mozart to the present Derivative files created: 5 (Box 1, Item 44)
    Contents: Mozart:Trio K. 498; Koechlin: Epitaph for Jean Harlow, op. 164; Brahms: Two songs, op. 91: Gestillte Sehnsucht -- Wiegenlied; Copland: Duo for flute and piano
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_044_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_044_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_044_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_044_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_044_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_044_01-05pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_044_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_044_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_044_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_044_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_044_01-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 45, 20 January 1972, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Cambiata Soloists 1972 Performers: Cambiata soloists, Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Mikhashoff, piano, harpsichord, director; David Bonner, flute; James Chamberlain, clarinet; Samuel Thiel, french horn; Harry Clark, cello; Rosemary Silversteen, violin; Wolfgang Justen, flute; Phyllis Herdliska, viola; Paul Schmidt, narrator Recording location: University of Texas at Austin, Department of Music Dolby Portion of concert titled From Shakespeare to Stravinsky Morley omitted, Trimble broken over two files Derivative files created: 5 (Box 1, Item 45)
    Contents: Brahms: The songs of Ophelia; Dowland: Lady, if you so spite me in darkness let me dwell; Morley: It was a lover and his lass; Weber: Trio, op. 63; Trimble: Four fragments from the Canterbury Tales
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_045_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_045_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_045_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_045_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_045_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_045_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_045_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_045_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_045_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_045_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_045_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_045_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 46, 15 June 1973, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Cambiata Soloists 1973 Performers: Cambiata Soloists: Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Diane Tobola, soprano; Amy Winn, flute; David Herbert, oboe; James Jeter, bassoon; Mikhashoff, piano, director Recording location: University at Texas at Houston Concert titled Voices and winds: music from Vivaldi to Hindemith Derivative files created: 9 (Box 1, Item 46)
    Contents: Vivaldi-Mikhashoff: Motetto O qui coeli; Vivaldi: Sonata pour flute et piano; Mikhashoff: Seis caprichos de Frederico Garcia Lorca -- The pipes of Colchis; David Ashley White: Duo for oboe and clarinet; Rodrigo: Cuatro madrigales amatorios; Kevin Pickard: Maculations on an old Irish Dumpe; Hindemith: Song for St. Martins's day; Ravel: Duet of the child and the princess -- Duet of the Wedgewood teapot and the china cup
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_046_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_046_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_046_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_046_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_046_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_046_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_046_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_046_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_046_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_046_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_046_02-06pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_046_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_046_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_046_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_046_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_046_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_046_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_046_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_046_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_046_02-06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 47, 4 November 1988, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Cambiata 1988 - 2 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Rice University Final two works on a concert titled New beginnings …(and endings). The preceding portion of the concert is on tape 48. Yes, 47 and 48 should have been the other way around but please leave as they are. Match Derivative files created: 2 (Box 1, Item 47)
    Contents: Charles Sepos: Blue temptation tango; Robert Berkman: Thorn-torn lips
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_047_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_047_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_047_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_047_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_047_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 48, 4 November 1988, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Cambiata 1988 - 1 Performers: Craig Bohmler, piano; Amy Winn, flute; Wendy Williams, flute; Janet Rarick, oboe; Christine Schaffer, piano; Ray Dillard, drums; Mikhashoff, piano; Toby Twining, singer Recording location: Rice University Program entitled: New Beginnings... (and Endings). Final two works of the program are on Tape 47. Program attached. Match Derivative files created: 12 (Box 1, Item 48)
    Contents: Bohmler: Sonata for flute, piano; Boone: A cool glow of radiation for flute, tape -- Zephyrus for oboe, piano -- The Watts towers for solo drummer; Curran: For Cornelius; Twining: Hee-oo-oom-ha -- For Satie -- In the stars from Three vocalizations; Sahl: Exiles café tango; Foss: Curriculum vitae tango; Pender: Tango: Ms. Jackson dances for the world; Cage: Perpetual tango; Duckworth: Tango voices
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_048_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_048_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_048_02-08pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_048_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_048_02-08sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 49, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Camenae + YM Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; David Kuehn, trumpet; Camenae Quartet Recording location: Burchfield Art Center (Buffalo, N.Y.) Match Derivative files created: 2 (Box 1, Item 49)
    Contents: Camargo Guarnieri: Ponteios no. 33, 24, 7; Shostakovich: Piano concerto no. 1
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_049_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_049_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_049_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_049_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_049_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 50, 18 March 1985, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Camenae + Y. M. Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Burchfield Art Center (Buffalo, N.Y.) Match Derivative files created: 5 (Box 1, Item 50)
    Contents: Mozart: Oboe quartet; Mikhashoff: Night dances; Hill, Jackson: Remembered landscape; Schumann: Scenes for childhood (arr. Mikhashoff; Martinu: Quartet
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_050_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_050_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_050_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_050_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_050_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_050_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_050_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_050_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_050_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_050_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_050_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_050_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 51, 24 April 1988, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Cohen Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Buffalo, N.Y.) Dolby B Tango Paseo written for Yvar Mikhashoff Match Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 51)
    Contents: Cohen: G -- Tango Paseo
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_051_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_051_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_051_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 52, 11 April 1979, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Concert in Paris Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: American Center, Paris (France) Contents from program need to be verified. Derivative files created: 9 (Box 2, Item 52)
    Contents: Wolff: Bread and roses; J. Sellars: Sonata for piano; Cowell: Banshee; Antheil: Sonata no. 3 (The death of machines); Ornstein: Wild men's dance; Griffes: Prelude; Ives: Three page sonata; B. McLean: Dimensions II; Valses pour piano (1977) with works by Fennimore, Felciano, Finney, Babbitt, Moran, Tower, Cage, Constanten, Wuorinen, Glass, and Thomson
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_052_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_052_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_052_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_052_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_052_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_052_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_052_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_052_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_052_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_052_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_052_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_052_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_052_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_052_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_052_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_052_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_052_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_052_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_052_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_052_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 53, 19 September 1976, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Contemporary Piano Concert #1 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Buffalo (N.Y.) First two works of concert (Liszt and Ravel) noted as being lost from the recording Derivative files created: 9 (Box 2, Item 53)
    Contents: Debussy: General Lavine -- Ce qu'a vu le vent d'ouest; Albeniz: El Albaicin; Debussy: Serenade; Ravel: Alborada; Debussy: Ondine; Ravel: Ondine; Debussy: Images II
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_053_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_053_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_053_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_053_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_053_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_053_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_053_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_053_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_053_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_053_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_053_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_053_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_053_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_053_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_053_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_053_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_053_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_053_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_053_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_053_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 54, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Copland / Rzewski Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Match Derivative files created: 2 (Box 2, Item 54)
    Contents: Copland: El salon Mexico (arr. Yvar Mikhashoff); Rzewski: Piano piece no. 4
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_054_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_054_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_054_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_054_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_054_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_054_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 55, 21 April 1990, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Costa '90 Rica Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Teatro Eugene O'Neill (San Jose, Costa Rica) Program titled Musica Americana para piano del moderna al post-moderna 01-07 is Curran incomplete; 02-01 is complete; 02-02-02-07 is foreign pop music Derivative files created: 14 (Box 2, Item 55)
    Contents: Copland: Three moods; Gershwin: Impromptu in two keys; Zappa: Piano introduction; Corea: Children's songs; Glass: Opening and modern love waltz; Rzewski: Piano piece no. 4; Curran: For Cornelius; Sahl: Exiles' café tango; Rudhyar: Tango d'Antan; Duckworth: Tango voices; Hill: Tango no tango; Berkman: Thorn-torn lips
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_055_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_055_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_055_02-07pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_055_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_055_02-07sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 56, 8 May 1988, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Curran Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Bang on a can (Music festival) (New York, N.Y.) Curran's For Cornelius listed on program, needs to be verified It is Curran Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 56)
    Contents: Curran: For Cornelius
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_056_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_056_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_056_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 57, 13 October 1988, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Curran program / Ijsbreker Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Ijsbreker (Amsterdam, Netherlands) Schtetl variations omitted? Derivative files created: 2 (Box 2, Item 57)
    Contents: Curran: Schtetl variations -- For Morton Feldman -- Hope street tunnel blues
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_057_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_057_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_057_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_057_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_057_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_057_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 58, 19 July 1990, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Darmstadt '90 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Darmstadt (Germany) Contents from program, need to be verified 12 files, 9 works? Scelsi works may each occupy a single file Derivative files created: 12 (Box 2, Item 58)
    Contents: Kurtag: Excerpts from Jatekok; Scelsi: Four illustrations; Sharman: Opera transcription no.1 (Madame Butterfly); Vigeland: Satie's sixth nocturne; Feldman: Intermission V; Young: Study no. 2; Bussotti: Morte di Fedra; Cage: Perpetual tango; Nancarrow: Tango?
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_058_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_058_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_058_02-10pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_058_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_02-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_02-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_058_02-10sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 59, 8 May 1988, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Davidovsky Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Bang on a can (Music festival) (New York, N.Y.) Dolby Only the Davidovsky Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 59)
    Contents: Davidovksy: Synchronisms VI; Curran: For Morton Feldman
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_059_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_059_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_059_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 60, 20 September 1978, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Denmark Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Kongelige Musikkonservatorium (Copenhagen, Denmark) Contents from printed program, need to be verified. Match Derivative files created: 7 (Box 2, Item 60)
    Contents: Wolff: Bread and roses; B. McLean: Dimensions II; L. Baker: Homage to D and Double; K. Law: Aurora borealis; Andriessen: Registers; Scelsi: 4 illustrazioni; Cage: Apartment house 1776 with solo
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_060_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_060_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_060_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_060_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_060_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_060_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_060_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_060_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_060_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_060_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_060_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_060_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_060_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_060_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_060_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_060_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 61, 19 June 1985, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Dutilleux Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Aldeburgh Festival of Music and the Arts (Aldeburgh, England) Note the label for Side B about playing the Perle work backwards and forwards. First two works of a concert that also included Ives's Sonata no. 2 Match Derivative files created: 2 (Box 2, Item 61)
    Contents: Dutilleux: Sonate (1947); Perle: Ballade
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_061_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_061_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_061_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_061_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_061_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_061_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 62, 16 November 1983, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Nov 16, 83 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Dolby B The contents on the label list another Norgaard work but the printed program lists the Sessions work stated in the contents. Match Derivative files created: 10 (Box 2, Item 62)
    Contents: Fennimore: Swann in Love; Stravinsky: Valse; Satie: Valse II; Antheil: Shimmy; Norgaard: Solo in intimo -- Solo in scena; Thomson: 12 portraits; Nancarrow: Sarabande and scherzo; Sessions: 6 pieces for cello solo; Rorem: Sonata in 4 scenes
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_062_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_062_02am.wav